db.questions.insert({ 
	name : 'American Trivia',
	questions: [
		{question : 'In the year 1900 in the U.S. what were the most popular first names given to boy and girl babies?', choices: ['William and Elizabeth', 'Joseph and Catherine', 'John and Mary', 'George and Anne'], correctAnswer: 2}, 
		{question : 'When did the Liberty Bell get its name?', choices: ['when it was made, in 1701', 'when it rang on July 4, 1776', 'in the 19th century, when it became a symbol of the abolition of slavery', 'none of the above'], correctAnswer: 2}, 
		{question : 'In the Roy Rogers -Dale Evans Museum, you will find Roy and Dales stuffed horses. Roy\'s horse was named Trigger, which was Dales horse?', choices: ['Buttermilk', 'Daisy', 'Scout', 'Tulip'], correctAnswer: 0}, 
		{question : 'The Daniel Boon museum at the home where he died can best be described how?', choices: ['a log cabin in Kentucky', 'a two-story clapboard house in Tennessee', 'a four-story Georgian-style home in Missouri', 'a three story brick house in Arkansas'], correctAnswer: 2}, 
		{question : ' Which of the following items was owned by the fewest U.S. homes in 1990?', choices: ['home computer', 'compact disk player', 'cordless phone', 'dishwasher'], correctAnswer: 1}, 
		{question : 'Who holds the record for the most victories in a row on the professional golf tour?', choices: ['Jack Nicklaus', 'Arnold Palmer', 'Byron Nelson', 'Ben Hogan'], correctAnswer: 2}, 
		{question : 'Who is third behind Hank Aaron and Babe Ruth in major league career home runs?', choices: ['Reggie Jackson', 'Harmon Killebrew', 'Willie Mays', 'Frank Robinson'], correctAnswer: 2}, 
		{question : 'In 1990, in what percentage of U.S. married couples did the wife earn more money than the husband?', choices: ['8', '18', '38', '58'], correctAnswer: 1}, 
		{question : 'During the 1980s for six consecutive years what breed of dog was the most popular in the U.S.?', choices: ['cocker spaniel', 'German shepherd', 'Labrador retriever', 'poodle.'], correctAnswer: 0}, 
		{question : 'In 1985, five percent of U.S. households had telephone answering machines. By 1990 what percentage of homes had answering machines?', choices: ['10 percent', '15 percent', '31 percent', '51 percent'], correctAnswer: 2}, 
		{question : 'The first black American pictured on a U.S. postage stamp was who?', choices: ['Frederick Douglass', 'Booker T. Washington', 'Louis Armstrong', 'Joe Louis'], correctAnswer: 3}, 
		{question : '2. What did the "D" in "D-Day" stand for?', choices: ['doom', 'day', 'Dwight (Eisenhower)', 'Dunkirk'], correctAnswer: 2}, 
		{question : '20. The Brownie Box Camera introduced by Eastman Kodak in 1900 had a retail price of what?', choices: ['$1', '$5', '$10', '$20'], correctAnswer: 0},
		{question : 'Which of these characters turned 40 years old in 1990?', choices: ['Charlie Brown', 'Bugs Bunny', 'Mickey Mouse', 'Fred Flintstone'], correctAnswer: 0}, 
		{question : 'The Philadelphia mint started putting a "P" mint mark on quarters when?', choices: ['1960', '1980', 'never'], correctAnswer: 1}, 
		{question : 'Before becoming George Bush\'s Secretary of Defense, what was Dick Cheney\'s position?', choices: ['congressman from Wyoming', 'governor of New Hampshire', 'secretary of defense under Ronald Reagan'], correctAnswer: 0}, 
		{question : 'When Mt. St. Helens erupted on May 18, 1980, how many people were killed?', choices: ['1', '57', '571'], correctAnswer: 1}, 
		{question : 'In J. Edgar Hoover, what did the J stand for?', choices: ['James', 'John', 'Joseph'], correctAnswer: 1}, 
		{question : 'Florence Nightingale became known as "the Lady With the Lamp" during which war?', choices: ['American Civil War', 'Crimean War', 'World War I'], correctAnswer: 1}, 
		{question : 'What year was it that the Census Bureau first reported that a majority of new mothers  were remaining in the new job market?', choices: ['1968', '1978', '1988'], correctAnswer: 2}
 	]
 });